[Music] As you go through
different stages of life,
life demands a lot from you.
[Music]
As your aspirations grow, so do your aspirations. From
travelling on public transport to building your
own home,
from renovating your home to meeting your children
's growing educational needs
and ensuring their higher education in the future. To
fulfil all these,
you need more than just saving; your savings need to grow over time.
[Music] A
simple regular premium payment plan can
accelerate your progress towards fulfilling your aspirations. It offers the
flexibility to choose between regular guaranteed
income or
a lump sum on maturity, which can help
fulfil the aspirations of your loved ones.
ICICI Proof Samriddhi
offers excellent features in every way. The comfort of
guaranteed growth in the form of compound bonuses and the
joy of
wealth growth in the form of a cycle method bonus.
You have the option to
withdraw the income at any time during the policy term.
You can also choose
a specific date of your choice to receive the income, making
your special moments
even more memorable.  You can make a premium. Not only this,
it
also provides you with the security of life cover during the entire policy term. The
best part is that you get all this
from a trusted brand that has
consistently announced bonuses on its policies for the last 16 years and has
given bonuses in excess of the promised bonuses, which have been availed by
one million policyholders. We are proud to help our
customers achieve progress and prosperity.
[Music] So, let
us explain these plan options in detail with some examples.
[Music]
Under the Income option,
a
guaranteed income is paid immediately after the completion of the premium payment term for the chosen period, followed by a bonus
on maturity. On the
other hand, if you are a 35-year-old male
and pay a premium of Rs 75,000 per year for 12 years,
you will
start receiving a guaranteed income of Rs 75,671 every year for the next 12 years.
At the end of the policy term, you
also get a maturity benefit of Rs 14.38 lakh at an AR of 8%,
while at an AR of 4%, the maturity
benefit will be Rs 3.50 lakh. Not only this, you
You also get the protection of life cover throughout the policy term. You choose to receive income today,
but your needs may change in the future
according to the changing circumstances of your life.
An innovative savings wallet included in the plan
also gives you the flexibility to accumulate your guaranteed income and
let it grow instead of taking it as income,
so that you can withdraw funds as per your needs.
This accumulated income can be withdrawn in
full or in part at any time during the policy term,
or under the lumpsum option,
a lump sum amount will be paid on maturity of the policy. For example,
if you are a 35-year-old male and
pay a premium of ₹50,000 for 10 years, the
maturity benefit at the end of the 20-year policy term at 8% will be ₹
7.51 lakh. Not only this, you also get the
protection of life cover throughout the policy term.
Bonus on Bonus
With the power of compounding, you get bonus on bonus.
This simply means that you get bonus on bonuses
paid as the bonuses compound as you achieve
your goals in life.  And as
ambitions change, you
need to keep pace with them.
With ICICI Prudential Sukh Samriddhi, you
can grow your savings and
live the life you want
[Music]